Finding aid for WUOM Records, 1914-1982
Bentley Historical Library
- Audio Material, 1930s-1970s
  - Sound Reels (7-inch)
    - U-M Sesquicentennial Celebration
      - Voices of Civilization Lecture Series, October 2-6, 1967 (Major Ceremony IV)
        - "The Shift of Power from East to West" / Dean Acheson, ([R143A-R145A]), 1967 October 02; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-42-1-1-1]; (Dean Acheson on the Voices of Civilization Lecture Series Recorded October 2, 1967, Broadcast December 1, 1967.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-42-1-1-2]; (Dean Acheson on the Voices of Civilization Lecture Series Recorded October 2, 1967, Broadcast December 1, 1967.)
          - [Reel3, Part 1], [8738-SR-42-1-1-3]; (Dean Acheson on the Voices of Civilization Lecture Series Recorded October 2, 1967, Broadcast December 1, 1967.)
    - State and Local History and Events
      - Interview with R.E. Olds; Development of Michigan's Auto Industry ([R146A]), 1950 April 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-43-1-1]; (WUOM State and Local History Events recordings: discussing the founding of REO and Oldsmobile auto companies.)
      - John F. Kennedy Campaign Speeches, 1960 October 13 (Box 21)
        - John F. Kennedy Speech at Willow Run Airport / Bill Huizenga, announcer, WCBN ([R147A]), 1960 October 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-44-1-1]; (John F. Kennedy Campaign Visit to Ann Arbor, First 1:30 commentary by reporter; ends with classical guitar music. Part of WUOM's State and Local History Events recordings.)
        - John F. Kennedy Speeches at [Willow Run] Airport and Michigan Union [and Ann Arbor Railway Station]; ([R148A]), 1960 October 13, 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 21)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-44-2-1]; (Recordings of Senator John F. Kennedy Campaign Visit to Ann Arbor and his speech outlining the idea of the Peace Corps. Part of WUOM's State and Local History Events recordings.)
        - John F. Kennedy Farewell Speech; ([R149A]), 1960 October 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-44-3-1]; (Recording of John F. Kennedy Campaign Visit to Ann Arbor with speeches by Senator Patrick McNamara, G. Mennen Williams, John B. Swainson. Part of WUOM's State and Local History Events recordings.)
      - Upper Peninsula Dialect Stories / Charles Follo, ([R150A]), [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-45-1-1]; (Lecture and examples of the tradition of dialect stories in the Upper Peninsula. Part of WUOM's State and Local History Events recordings.)
  - Sound Reels (10.5 inch)
    - WUOM: Anniversary and Dedication Programs, WVGR
      - Anniversary and Dedication Programs, [R151B-152B]; 2 reels (Box 21)
      - WUOM Dedication Week Variety Show, January14, 1950; [R153B] (Box 22)
        (Dedication of WUOM-FM and 25th anniversary celebration of UMBS, Robert Q. Lewis and Steve Filipiak, hosts; Ward Quaal; Bob Ufer; Mary Bell; et al., original recording January 14, 1950, dub November 16, 1964 broadcast live January 14, 1950)
      - Tenth Anniversary Program, recorded, July 3, 1958; [R154B-R155B]; 2 reels (Box 22)
        (broadcast Panorama July 5, 1958 Partial script in WUOM paper records series)
    - WUOM: Original Productions
      - "The American Town: A Self-Portrait"
        - "The American Town: A Self-Portrait" Program #3: "The Copper Country" ([R156B-r157B]), 1966 February 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-46-1-1-1]; (Part 1 of 2; Recorded February 16, 1966, Broadcast April 6, 1966. In Houghton and Keweenaw Counties: Mining and Mills in Upper Peninsula; Interviews with former miners and residents of mining towns in Calumet, Quincy Mine, Eagle Project and others; also discusses lumber industry in Upper Peninsula; concludes with a discussion of pastimes and faith in the Upper Peninsula.)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-46-1-1-2]; (Part 2 of 2; Recorded February 16, 1966, Broadcast April 6, 1966. Life in the Keweenaw Peninsula (Hancock and Houghton Michigan); prohibition; music (Kantele); copper mining and labor unions; Italian Hall Disaster, Ku Klux Klan; food; schools in Keweenaw)
        - "The American Town: A Self-Portrait" Program #5: Durand, Michigan ([R158B]), 1964 December 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-46-2-1]; (Recorded December 16, 1964, Broadcast March 18, 1965. Locomotives in Durand; life in Durand; religious intolerance and the KKK; Circus Trainwreck of 1903; labor disputes; "tramps" and "hobos" riding the trains; lynching incidents in Durand; schools in Durand; decline of the railroad.)
      - (Anthology of of Interviews) [Christiaan Barnard on Heart Transplants; Robben Fleming on BAM and demands for higher education] ([R159B]), 1968 January 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-47-1-1-1]; (Anthology of interviews, dubbed June 12, 1971. Press conference with Christiaan Barnard March 6, 1968; First Heart Transplant, University of Michigan Hospital, September 23, 1968.)
        - [Part 2], [8738-SR-47-1-1-2]; (December 3, 1968; Press conference with Robben W. Fleming; On Draft and Student Grades, tutition for in-state and out-of-state students; athletics. January 3, 1968; Robben W. Fleming Meeting with BAM; CBS Interview with Robben W. Fleming April 15, 1968, Student unrest: S. I. Hayakawa, President of San Francisco State College; Robben Fleming of U of M; Morris Abram President of Brandeis University]; Press conference with Robben W. Fleming in Traverse City [MI], July 24, 1969; last 6 minutes discusses student radicalism.)
      - "A Dickens of A Christmas" ([R160B]), 1970 December 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-52-1-1]; (Recorded December 23, 1970, Broadcast December 24, 1970; Bert Hornback; Lord Chamberlain's Players; music by Quin Adamson, prepared by the Broadcasting Service.)
      - [Michigan Men in the Civil War] Program ([R161B-R163B]), 1961 July 15; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
        - [Reel 1, Part 1, Program #1: The First Battle of Bull Run], [8738-SR-53-1-1-1]; (Dramatization of Michigan Civil War stories, Russell E. Bidlack, broadcast Panorama, July 15, 1961)
        - [Reel 2, Part 1, Program #2: Prisoner of War Experiences], [8738-SR-53-1-1-2]; (Dramatization of Michigan Civil War stories, Russell E. Bidlack, reading of letters and documentary from the Civil War, broadcast Panorama, July 29, 1961)
        - [Reel 3, Part ,1 Program #3: The Lighter Side of the War], [8738-SR-53-1-1-3]; (Dramatization of Michigan Civil War stories, Russell E. Bidlack, reading of letters and documentary from the Civil War, broadcast Panorama. August 12, 1961)
      - "The News from Dallas"/ Fred Hindley, narrator ([R164B]), 1964 November 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-54-1-1]; (On the assassination of John F. Kennedy and international reactions.)
      - News in 20th Century America
        - News in 20th Century America Program #4: Women in Journalism ([R165B]), 1959 February 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-55-1-1]; (Documentary: Leland Stowe, host (broadcast June-October 1959) with Doris Fleeson. Speakers are: Leland Stowe; Pauline Frederick; Sylvia Porter; et al.)
        - News in 20th Century America Program #13: The Columnist: Pressures and Problems ([R166B]), 1959 April 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 22)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-55-2-1]; (Panelists are: Roscoe Drummond, Frank Angelo, Sylvia Porter, and Drew Pearson. Radio program documenting the history and structure of journalism in the 20th century.)
      - One Nation Indivisible Program
        (award-winning documentary]--broadcast March-May 1958 (2 reels of 13 retained)
        - One Nation Indivisible Program #1: The Rise of Nationalism ([R167B]), 1958 March 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-56-1-1]; (Re-Broadcast March-May 1958, One Nation Indivisible, award-winning documentary.)
        - One Nation Indivisible Program #13: Internationalism ([R168B]), 1958 March 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-56-2-1]; (One Nation Indivisible; award-winning documentary; re-broadcast March-May 1958.)
      - They Fought Alone
        - They Fought Alone - Program #3: Elizabeth Blackwell ([R169B]), 1953 October 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-57-1-1]; ("They Fought Alone" was an award-winning drama-documentary. Stories were based on the lives of men and women who fought for the freedom to know. Blackwell was the first woman admitted to medical school in the United States.)
      - Union Sesquicentennial, Documentary history of Michigan Union ([R170B]), 1954 October 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-58-1-1]; (Radio program and dramatization about the history of the Michigan Union.)
    - WUOM: Program Series
      - Symposium, 1973-1975, 9 reels
        (monthly studio interview/public forum program on topics of interest to University of Michigan faculty, staff, students, and administrators], broadcast September 1972-April 1975, academic year only)
        - 1973 (Box 23)
          - Symposium '73 "The Economic Future of the University of Michigan" ([R171B]), 1973 September 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-1-1]; (President Fleming; Prof. Harold Johnson; David Fowler, Adm V.P. of Student Council speaking.)
          - Symposium '73 "Faculty-Staff Salaries" ([R172B]), 1973 October 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-2-1]; (Speakers include: Allen F. Smith; Ralph Loomis.)
          - Symposium '73 "Women's Athletics" ([R173B]), 1973 November 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-3-1]; (Speakers are: Robben W. Fleming, Eunice Burns, and Sheryl Szady.)
          - Symposium '73 "Student Government" ([R174B]), 1973 December 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-4-1]; (Speakers are: Robben W. Fleming, Henry Johnson, and Kathleen Kolar.)
        - Symposium 1974
          - Symposium '74 "Fuel Shortage" ([R175B]), 1974 January 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-5-1]; (Speakers are: Robben W. Fleming, Don Wendall, and Dan Bluggerman.)
          - Symposium '74 "Technology and Education" ([R176B]), 1974 February 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-6-1]; (Speakers are: Robben W. Fleming, Bernard Galler, and Tony Morris, by phone.)
          - Symposium '74 "Student Financial Aid" ([R177B]), 1974 March 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-7-1]; (Speakers are: Tom Butts, Joseph Kosand, and Dan Biddle.)
          - Symposium '74 "Unionization at University of Michigan" ([R178B]), 1974 March 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-8-1]; (Khosted by Hazen Schumacher. Speakers are: Robben W. Fleming, Carl Cohen, Dan Biddle.)
        - 1975
          - Symposium '75: A look at the 1975/76 academic year ([R179B]), 1975 January 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-59-9-1]; (Speakers are: Robben W. Fleming, Frank H.T. Rhodes, and Wilbur K. Pierpont.)
    - U-M Ceremonies and Convocations
      - Award Presentation and Banquet Address ([R180B]), 1968 November 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-60-1-1]; (On the subject of income maintenance and the Social Security System Conference, November 10-12, 1968. Speakers are: Wilbur J. Cohen, Robben W. Fleming, et al.)
      - Commencement 1962: Address by Robert S. McNamara ([R181B]), 1962 June 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 23)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-61-1-1]; (Broadcast of 1962 commencement exercises. Includes Robert McNamara's commencement address.)
      - Commencement 1964: Address by Lyndon B. Johnson 'The Great Society' Speech ([R182B]), 1964 May 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch (Box 23)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-127-1-1]; (Broadcast of 1964 commencement exercises. Lyndon B. Johnson gives commencement speech and receives honorary degree.)
      - Commencement 1966: Address by John Kenneth Galbraith ("Foreign Policy, Politics, and the University") ([R183B]), 1966 April 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-62-1-1]; (Broadcast of 1966 Commencement Exercises.)
      - Commencement 1974: Address by Gerald R. Ford ([R184B]), 1974 May 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-63-1-1]; (Broadcast of 1974 commencement exercises. Address given by Gerald R. Ford.)
      - Commencement 1976, Winter: Address by Betty Ford, Wilbur K. Pierpont ([R185B]), 1976 December 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-64-1-1]; (Broadcast of 1976 commencement exercises. Address given by Wilbur K. Pierpont. Betty Ford receives honorary degree.)
      - Dedication Address: Peace Corps Plaque Dedication ([R186B]), 1964 May 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-65-1-1]; (Peace Corps Plaque Dedication Address; Harlan H. Hatcher introduces Cleveland; Erich Walter, includes clip from original Kennedy speech.)
      - Bentley Historical Library Dedication "Local History is Alive and Well" ([R187B]), 1974 May 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-128-1-1]; (Recording of the Bentley Historical Library Dedication. Event included several speakers; [includes paper insert])
      - Dedication Ceremony: Institute for Social Research ([R188B]), 1966 March 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-66-1-1]; (George Romney, Marvin L. Niehuss, and Rensis Likert dedicating the Institute for Social Research building.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Mental Health Research Institute ([R189B-R189B]), 1960 January 30; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Reel 1. Part 1], [8738-SR-67-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Speaking about dedication of the Mental Health Research Institute and subsequent conference.)
        - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-67-1-1-2]; (Tape 2 of 2; Speaking about dedication of the Mental Health Research Institute and subsequent conference.)
      - School of Music Dedication Ceremony ([R191B]), 1964 September 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-68-1-1]; (Dedication Ceremony, featuring: Dean Wallace; Harlan H. Hatcher; Aline Saarinen; Honorary degree presentation to Aline Saarinen, Aaron Copland, Leonard Bernstein, Earl V. Moore; Michigan Men's Glee Club, Michigan Band directed by Revelli, Copland,and Bernstein.)
      - Freshman Orientation Convocation; President Harlan H. Hatcher ([R192B]), 1966 August 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-69-1-1]; (Freshman Convocation includes performance with "The Friars"; PA bug ends with intro to the Friars.)
      - Honorary Degree Convocation: James A. McDivitt and Edward H. White; Dedication Ceremony: Space Research Laboratory ([R193B]), 1965 June 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-70-1-1]; (James A. McDivitt and Edward H. White dedication of the Space Research Laboratory shortly after the Gemini 4 flight.)
      - Memorial Service: Martin Luther King ([R194B]), 1968 April 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-71-1-1]; (Memorial service for Martin Luther King held at Hill Auditorium. Speakers include: / Allan F. Smith; Albert Wheeler; Samuel Jones; Emmett Green; William Haber; Opal Bailey; Magit [sic] Downs.)
    - U-M Conferences and Lectures
      - Alumni University
        - Speech ("Today's Faculty") / Roger W. Heyns, recorded, April 29, 1965; [R195B] (Box 24)
          (broadcast Lecture Hour August 5, 1965)
      - Anti-War Rally (various local sponsors), 1972 (Box 24)
        - Informal speeches / Dave Dellinger, et al.([R196B]), 1972 October 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-72-1-1]; (Anti-War Rally - Informal speeches by Dave Dellinger (back from Hanoi) and others at anti-war rally.)
      - Creative Arts Festival, 1961
        - "The Aesthetic Vacuum of Our Age" / Ayn Rand ([R197B]), 1961 May 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 24)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-73-1-1]; (Ayn Rand lecturing at the Creative Arts Festival.)
        - John Ciardi ([R198B]), 1961 May 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-74-1-1]; (Creative Arts Festival; John Ciardi reads "The Artist" by William Carlos Williams, "Showing A Foreigner Through His Studio, Leonardo Answers A Question", "Elegy Just in Case", "A Memory of the Sad Chair", "The Eleventh Hour News", "A Dialog in the Shade" "Hamlet in the Wings", "Launcelot in Hell", "Bedlam Revisited", unknown poem about whittling, "I Said to the Bug in the Sink", "The Cat Heard the Cat Bird", "The Dolls", "The Sea Shines", "In The Garden of the Hurricane's Eye", concludes with various epitaphs written by Ciardi.)
        - Robert Penn Warren ([R199B]), 1965 March 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-75-1-1]; (Creative Arts Festival, Robert Penn Warren reads "Original Sin", "The Ballad of Billie Potts", "To A Little Girl, One Year Old, in A Ruined Fortress.")
        - Robert Lowell ([R200B]), 1965 March 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-76-1-1]; (Broadcast September 09 1965, Creative Arts Festival; includes paper insert; Robert Lowell reads unknown poem, "Mr. Edwards and the Spider", "Falling Asleep Over the Aeneid", "Elegy on Ford Madox Ford", "Memories of West Street and Lepke", translations of Boris Pasternak poems, "Middle Age", "Fall 1961", "The Neo-Classical Urn", "For The Union Dead.")
        - W. D. Snodgrass ([R201B]), 1966 March 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 15 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-77-1-1]; (W.D. Snodgrass reads "Take Off", "Regraduating the Lute", "Green Huntsman", "The Platform Man", "Edmund to Gloucester", "After Experience Taught Me...", "The Mouse", "Fourth of July", "The Survivors", "The Men's Room in the College Chapel", "Matisse: The Red Studio", "The Mother and Sister of the Artist", "Manet: Execution of Emperor Maximilian", "Monet: "Les Nymphéas.")
      - Department of Classical Studies
        - Reading [original translation of Aeschylus's "Agamemnon") / Robert Lowell ([R202B]), 1966 January 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-78-1-1]; (Robert Lowell reads Aeschylus's "Agamemnon")
      - Department of English
        (Recordings were broadcast as part of Lecutre Hour program, 1958-1965)
        - Robert Creeley; introduced by Donald Hall ([R203B]), 1964 November 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-79-1-1]; (Robert Creeley reads "The Innocence", "After Lorca", "The Moral Proposition", "The Operation", "Chanson", "The Warning", "The Naughty Boy", "The Whip", "A Form of Women", "The Three Ladies", "Goodbye", "The Wind", "A Marriage", "The Rhythm", "The Rocks", unfinished poem, "Anger", "The Woman", "If You", "The Rose", "The Rain", "The Hill", "The Name", "For Love.")
        - James Wright; introduced by Donald Hall ([R204B]), 1958 October 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-80-1-1]; (James Wright reads Thomas Hardy: "During Wind and Rain" (cuts out briefly), Vassar Miller, "Unspoken Dialogue", Emily Dickinson, "I Cannot Live With You", Emily Brontë "Cold In The Earth", his own poems: "Father", "Lament for My Brother on a Hayrake" ,"To A Defeated Savior", "A Poem About George Doty in the Death House", "A Tunnel", "My Grandmother's Ghost", "Old Man Drunk", unknown poem, "The Alarm", "The Morality of Poetry", Theodore Roethke "Academics", Lord Byron "When a man hath no freedom to fight for at home", Jonathan Swift "On Burning A Dull Poem", William Blake epigrams, nursery rhymes.)
        - Denise Levertov ([R205B]), 1962 April 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-81-1-1]; (Broadcast August 30,1962, Introduced by Donald Hall, Denise Levertov reads from "Jacob's Ladder", "The World Outside", unknown poem, "The Part", "The Sequence" in five parts, "Six Variations", "Come Into Animal Presence", "Song for a Dark Voice", Five poems from Mexico: "The Weave", "Corazon", "The Rose", "Canticle", "Sierra"; "The Well", "The Tulips", "The Gracenote", "The Breathing", "Living with a Painting", "The Film", "Sparks", "A Cure of Souls", "Another Spring", "The Ache of Marriage", "Kingdoms of Heaven", "To The Snake.")
        - Robert Bly; introduced by Donald Hall ([R206B]), 1962 November 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-82-1-1]; (Broadcast January 16, 1963, Robert Bly reads "Hunting Pheasants in a Cornfield", "September Night with An Old Horse", "The Busy Man Speaks", "Snow in March", "Sleet Storm on the Merritt Parkway", "Looking Backward", "Poem in Three Parts", "Late At Night During a Visit of Friends", "A Walk in the Gardens of Italy" by I.M. Baroque, 5 Kobayashi Issa poems, "Saturday Night", "The Crow", "Unanswered Letters", "Watering A Horse", "Poem for a Love Poem", "Taking the Hands of Someone You Love", "At The Funeral of Great Aunt Mary", "Poem on Norwegian Immigrants", "Afternoon Sleep", "Condition of the Working Classes, 1960", "After the Industrial Revolution, All Things Happen at Once", reads a Yeats song, "Through the Woods", "Evolution from the Fishes.")
        - John Hollander ([R207B]), 1962 December 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-83-1-1]; (Broadcast February 28, 1963, English Department Lecture John Hollander reads "The Ladies' Maid Song", "A Whole Story", "Race Rock Light", "Digging It Out", "To The Lady Portrayed by Margaret Dumont", "Movie Going", "Riddle and Answer", "The Great Bear", "Making It", Two Meditative Landscapes", "Humming", "The Cold Surprise of Fall Rain", "Helicon.")
        - John Woods; introduced by Mark Spilka ([R208B]), 1963 February 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-84-1-1]; (John Woods reads "On Modification", "The Visits of My Aunt", "Barney's Sister", "Everything Slumps At Kreiner's Pier", "Suburban Note", "The Log of the Ark", "Acclamation", "Told then Told Again", "Main Scene", "What Do You Do When It's Spring?", "The Gathering", "Vacation", "Stillwater", "Terrible is the Child", "An Afternoon of Themes", "Uncle", "To The Waiters for Miracles.")
        - Robert Bly ([R209B]), 1963 November 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)